Florence Hollis and Rosemary Ross Reynolds Papers, 1863-1987
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- Series VII. TYPOLOGY RESEARCH
  - Notes and findings
    - Classification System, general case notes and discussion notes, ca. 194[?]-196[?], ca. 1986 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Classification System, general cases notes and discussion notes, ca. 1954-1958 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Pre-book Classification Study, samples of notes on cases, Watson, ca. 1953-1957 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Pre-book Classification Study, sample of notes on cases, Kerr, ca. 1954-1958 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Classification outlines, schemes, charts and item illustrations, 1958-ca. 1974 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - 1966 typology work folders and related documents
    - "1966 Work Folder, findings, material for computer"
      - ca. 196[?]-1966 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - ca. 1962-1966 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - ca. 1962-1966 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - ca. 1962-1966 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - "Notes for summer work, 1966," ca. 1966 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Program for the Wilcoxon and Mann-Whitney Tests and related materials, ca. 1965-1966 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Classification in Casework Treatment, notes and tables, 1964-ca. 1966 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - National Institute of Mental Health reports and related documents
    - Typology research development, ideas, progress reports, grant applications and correspondence, 1958-1966, ca. 1986 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - "Development of A Casework Treatment Typology," Final Progress Report, 1-50A, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - "Development of A Casework Treatment Typology," Final Progress Report, 51-84 and appendices, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - "Development of A Casework Treatment Typology," Final Report, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - "A Casework Treatment Typology Workbook," 1968 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - "A Casework Treatment Typology Workbook," revisions and notes, ca. 1968 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Cases used in typology research
    - Records and code sheets
      - Case 1, 1962-1964, ca. 1971 (Box 44, Folder 19)
      - Case 2, 1962-1964, ca. 1971 (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - Case 3, 1963-1964, ca. 1971 (Box 44, Folder 21)
      - Case 4, 1962-1965 (Box 44, Folder 22)
      - Case 5, 1962-1964, ca. 1971 (Box 44, Folder 23)
      - Case 6, 1962-1964, ca. 1971 (Box 44, Folder 24)
      - Case 7, 1962-1964, ca. 1971 (Box 44, Folder 25)
      - Case 8, 1962-1964, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 26)
      - Case 9, 1963-1964, ca. 1971 (Box 44, Folder 27)
      - Record 173485, 1962-1971 (Box 44, Folder 28)
      - Record 173486 and record 174373, 1962-1963 (Box 44, Folder 29)
      - Miscellaneous notes, ca. 1962-1971 (Box 44, Folder 30)
      - Training kit, assorted materials, 1962-ca. 1967 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Diagnostic records and interview data
      - Family and Children's Service, St. Louis, MO
        - 1001, case 144236, ca. 1966 (Box 44, Folder 32)
        - 1002, case 144237, ca. 1966 (Box 44, Folder 33)
        - 1003, case 144607, ca. 1966-1968 (Box 44, Folder 34)
        - 1004, case 144369, ca. 1966 (Box 44, Folder 35)
        - 1005, case 146036, ca. 1967 (Box 44, Folder 36)
        - 1006, ca. 1967 (Box 44, Folder 37)
        - 1007, ca. 1967 (Box 44, Folder 38)
        - 1008, ca. 1967 (Box 44, Folder 39)
        - 1009, case 146814, 1967? (Box 44, Folder 40)
        - 1010, ca. 1966-1967 (Box 44, Folder 41)
        - 1011 case 146237, ca. 1967 (Box 44, Folder 42)
        - 1012 case 146640, ca. 1967 (Box 44, Folder 43)
      - Family Service of Philadelphia
        - 1021, case 55809, ca. 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 44)
        - 1022, case 55837, ca. 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 45)
        - 1023, case 55548, ca. 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 46)
        - 1024, case 55848, 1966-1967? (Box 45, Folder 47)
        - 1025, case 56065, ca. 1967 (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - Typology speeches and papers
    - Hollis's typology, speeches, papers and notes, ca. 1957-1967 (Box 45, Folder 49)
    - Administrative Group Meeting, minutes and notes, Family Service Association of Cleveland, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 50)
    - "The Relation of Diagnosis to Treatment Techniques," speech, related notes and flyer, N.A.S.W., 1962-1964 (Box 45, Folder 51)
    - "Casework Treatment: An Attempt at Classification" and "Casework Treatment: Experiment in Classifications," lecture, notes and program, Chicago and Cincinnati, ca. 1964-1965 (Box 45, Folder 52)
    - "Explorations with a Treatment Typology," program and commentary, Bryn Mawr College, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 53)
    - "Developments in Casework Methodology," speech notes, National Institute for Social Work Training, London, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 54)
  - Papers, studies, and articles using the Hollis typology
    - Comparison of Hollis's typology with other systems, ca. 1963-1964, ca. 1986 (Box 45, Folder 55)
    - Reid-Turner coding study, record T1, interview transcript and code sheets, ca. 1963-1965, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 56)
    - Classification resource material, 8201, ca. 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 57)
    - "Social Work Treatment and Values Differences," Francis Turner, doctoral dissertation, 1963
      - Chapters 1-3 (Box 45, Folder 58)
      - Chapters 4-7 (Box 45, Folder 59)
      - Appendices, bibliography and Hollis's notes, 1963-[1971?] (Box 45, Folder 60)
    - Final report of project 555-25-1, Francis Turner, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 61)
    - "An Investigation of a Scheme for the Classification of Casework Activities," Domanski, et al., Smith School for Social Work, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 62)
    - "The Application of the Hollis Treatment Classification System to the Casework Treatment of Adolescents," Barbara Ennis, master's thesis, New York School of Social Work, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 63)
    - "Treatment Procedures Used With Schizophrenic Patients, Chronic, Undifferentiated Type," M.K. O'Neill, master's thesis, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 64)
    - "The Use of Content Analysis to Compare Three Types of Casework Recording," Buchenhorner, et al., Columbia University School of Social Work, 1966
      - Part I (Box 46, Folder 65)
      - Part II and bibliography (Box 46, Folder 66)
    - "Situational Diagnosis and Situational Therapy," Max Siporin, paper, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 67)
    - "Casework Treatment Procedures as a Function of Client-Diagnostic Variables," Edward J. Mullen, doctoral dissertation, 1968
      - Chapters 1-4 (Box 46, Folder 68)
      - Chapters 5-7 (Box 46, Folder 69)
      - Appendices and bibliography (Box 46, Folder 70)
    - "Testing with a Treatment Typology," Edna Chamberlain, paper and correspondence, with commentary by Florence Hollis, 1968-ca. 1969 (Box 46, Folder 71)
    - Service to Youth Council, code manual, correspondence and related material, ca. 1969 (Box 46, Folder 72)
    - Typology coding with Mitzi Montgomery, correspondence, interview and analysis, ca. 1971-1973, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 73)
    - "Feedback Systems, Interaction Analysis, and Counseling Models in Professional Programmes," Mitzi Montgomery, doctoral dissertation, 1973
      - Chapters 1-4 (Box 47, Folder 74)
      - Chapters 5-7 (Box 47, Folder 75)
      - Chapter 8, bibliography and appendices (Box 47, Folder 76)
    - Preventing Chronic Dependency, Mullen, et al.
      - Draft, chapters 1-6, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 77)
      - Draft, chapters 7-9 and appendices, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 78)
    - Preventing Chronic Dependency, Mullen, et al., publication and notes, Community Service Society of New York, ca. 1970 (Box 47, Folder 79)
      - Hollis's comments, 1970-1973 (Box 47, Folder 80)
    - "Caseworkers' Judgments of Clients' Hope: Some Correlates among Client-Situation Characteristics and Among Workers' Communication Patterns," F.L. Boatman, doctoral dissertation, 1974
      - Chapters 1-3 (Box 47, Folder 81)
      - Chapters 4-5, appendices and bibliography (Box 47, Folder 82)
    - "Developing A Research Methodology for Theory Research in a Project: A Classification System that Predicts Casework Treatment," and related work, Donald Ayre, Family and Children's Service, Pittsburgh, 1963-1964 (Box 48, Folder 83)
    - "A Classification System that Predicts Casework Methodology," Donald Ayre, Family and Children's Service, Pittsburgh, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 84)
    - "The Hollis Typology Applied to an Inner City Population," Ron Spolar, paper and correspondence, ca. 1975-1976 (Box 48, Folder 85)
    - "The Hollis Typology Applied to an Inner City Population," Ron Spolar, paper and correspondence, ca. 1975-1976 Lee Rauch, paper and correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 48, Folder 86)
    - Published articles using Hollis typology, 1964-1970 (Box 48, Folder 87)
- Series VIII. NOTES ON SELECTED DOCUMENTS
  - Key to folders, ca. 1986 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - "Scattered Teaching Notes"
    - Folder 1, ca. 1930s, ca. 1986 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Folder 2, consultation with Dr. Maider, notes, ca. 1933, ca. 1986 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Folder 3, ca. 1930s, ca. 1986 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Folder 4, casework, "spiral notebook," ca. 1936-1939, ca. 1986 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Notes for speeches, 1930-1940
    - Folder 5, "The Caseworker and the Modern Family," and "Individualized Service to Families," 1938, ca. 1986 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Folder 6, Edwards family, ca. 1936-1939, ca. 1986 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Folder 7, ca. 1930-1940, ca. 1986 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Folder 8, On curriculum changes, ca. 1938, ca. 1986 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Folder 9, "Why a Private Family Agency?," ca. 1930-1940, ca. 1986 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Folder 10, On supervision, ca. 1930-1940, ca. 1986 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Folder 11, Cash versus kind, ca. 1930-1940, ca. 1986 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Folder 12, "Making the Most of Our Children," ca. 1930-1940, ca. 1986 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Folder 13, "Making the Most of Our Children," final version, ca. 1930-1940, ca. 1986 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Folder 14, Speech on attitudes, 1939, ca. 1986 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Folder 15, "The Place of the Private Family Welfare Society in the Community," 1938, ca. 1986 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Folder 16, "Private and Public Relief," ca. 1937-1939, ca. 1986 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Folder 17, Social Case Work in Practice: Six Case Studies, case notes, ca. 1930s, ca. 1976 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Folder 18, comments on Helen Perlman's book, 1958, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Tapes
    - 1, 2, and 3, ca. 1986 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - 4, notes on Helen Perlman's book, and 5, notes on Casework in Practice: Six Case Studies, ca. 1985-1986 (Box 48, Folder 21)
- Series IX. PHOTOGRAPHS
  - Florence Hollis collection
    - Florence Hollis, ca. 1910-1987, undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Florence Hollis, school photographs, ca. 1922-1928, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Louis Herbert Hollis and Bertha Hoerig Hollis, parents of Florence Hollis, 1954-1986, undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Louis Hoerig Hollis, brother of Florence Hollis and his wife, Virginia Earle Hollis, 1915, 1944-1964, undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Hoerig relatives, 1918, 1964, undated (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Hollis relatives, 1941-1952, undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Florence Hollis and Rosemary Reynolds, 1937-1979, undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Friends and associates of Florence Hollis and Rosemary Reynolds, C-S, 1946-1982, undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Friends and associates of Florence Hollis and Rosemary Reynolds, T-W, and unidentified, ca. 1920-1987 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Florence Day, 1947-1954, undated (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Anni Hofer and Ruth Zobrist, 1951-1985, undated (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Dame Eileen Younghusband, 1958-1978, undated (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Crosslands Retirement Community, Kennett Square, Pennsylvania, 1978-1980 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Unidentified and miscellaneous, 1905, 1963-1986, undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Rosemary Reynolds collection
    - Rosemary Reynolds, 1906-1971, undated (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Mary Ross Reynolds and Chauncey P. Reynolds, parents of Rosemary Reynolds, 1901-1903, undated (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Reynolds family members, 1903-1911, ca. 1960-1975, undated (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Home of Mary Ross Reynolds, 6105 Wayne Avenue, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1939, 1961, 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Assorted friends and relatives [?], ca. 1928-1973 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Mount Holyoke College classmates, 1928, 1953, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Office, Community Service Society of New York, 1968-1978 (Box 50, Folder 21)
- Series X. ROSEMARY REYNOLDS PAPERS
  - Family history and biography
    - Reynolds family tree, newsclippings and related documents, 1967-1979, undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Bridal register and marriage certificate, Mary Ross Reynolds and Chauncey P. Reynolds, 1901-1902 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Birth certificate and notice, and confirmation paper, 1906, 1922 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - "The Biography of Our Baby," 1906-1912 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - "The Biography of Our Baby," enclosures, 1906-1912, undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Biographical materials, ca. 1930-1981 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Certificates and awards, 1934-1935, ca. 1973 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Diary of a friend or relative of Rosemary Reynolds, ca. 1939-1946, undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Mary Ross Reynolds, assorted materials, 1940-1964, undated (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence to Mary Ross Reynolds, ca. 1958-1962, undated (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Medical records, 1968-1980, undated (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Retirement at Crosslands, Kennett Square, Pennsylvania
      - Correspondence with Crosslands, 1972-1977 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - Committee records, ca. 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 13)
      - Hospice group workshop, memos, questionnaire and relfections, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Religious pamphlets, prayers and related documents, undated (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence
    - General correspondence, 1922-1928 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - General corrrespondence, 1955-1984, undated (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence records, 1949-1984 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Address list from 1903 to 1961, ca. 1942-1961 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Education
    - High School
      - English notebook, pages 1-101, 1922 (Box 51, Folder 20)
      - English notebook, pages 102-192, 1922 (Box 51, Folder 21)
      - "The Diary of the Winthrop Family," fictional diary chronicling the period from 1620-1920, 1923[?] (Box 52, Folder 22)
      - "Modern Poetry," paper, April 27, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Graduate study in London
      - "New Homes for London's Poor," 1928 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Pennsylvania School of Social Work
      - Case summary, 1929, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 25)
      - "Casework for First Years," Master of Social Work thesis, 1936 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Community Service Society of New York
      - Culture and personality seminar, notes, reports and related material, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Publications, papers, and speeches
    - The Spokesman, Family Society of Philadelphia, 1931-1933 (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Publications, papers and speeches, ca. 1931-1933, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Publication, papers and speeches, 1934-1938 (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - Publications, papers, speeches and reviews, 1946-1947 (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - "Services to Individuals Within a Group Work Setting," speech, correspondence and related report, 1950-1951 (Box 52, Folder 32)
    - Publications, papers, and speech, 1951-1959 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - Professional activities
    - Atlantic City, Institute on selection and supervision of student supervisors, conference notes, 1950, ca. 1947-1950 (Box 52, Folder 34)
    - Bryn Mawr Institute June 1955, Unmarried parenthood, records, notes and final summary, 1951-1955 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Cleveland, Ohio, Supervisory conferences, ca. 1934-1937 (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Community Service Society of New York
      - Assorted documents, 1942-1975 (Box 53, Folder 37)
      - Committee on student training and supervision, minutes, memoranda, progress reports and related documents, 1947-1948, undated (Box 53, Folder 38)
      - Study of professional responsibilities in family service, memoranda and reports, ca. 1947-1949 (Box 53, Folder 39)
      - Intake study, minutes and reports, 1949-1950 (Box 53, Folder 40)
      - DS-AS Committee of the Whole, minutes and memoranda, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 41)
      - Case review study, memos and reports, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 42)
      - Progress report, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 43)
      - Study committee report and related newsclipping, January 1971 (Box 53, Folder 44)
      - Caring for the aged, reports and publication, The Natural Supports Program, 1980-1981 (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - "Content of Field Work Training in a Family Agency," on supervision, notes, 1942-1946 (Box 53, Folder 46)
    - Cuyahoga County Relief Administration (CCRA), Cleveland, Ohio, Studies, reports and correspondence, 1934-1937 (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - Family Service Association of America seminar, "Philosophy and Practice of Supervision," Lake Forest, Illinois, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 48)
    - Family Welfare Society of America, Great Lakes region, supervision, assorted documents, 1926-1929, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 49)
    - Guidelines for staff development programs, on supervision, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 50)
    - Institute of Family Services (The Associated Charities), Cleveland, Ohio, Correspondence, 1933 (Box 53, Folder 51)
    - Smith College School for Social Work, Institute on student supervision, notes, July 1946 (Box 53, Folder 52)
    - Smith College School for Social Work, Supervisory method in social casework seminar, conference notes, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 53)
    - Western Reserve University, School of Applied Social Sciences, staff supervision conference notes, 1937-1942 (Box 53, Folder 54)
    - Western Reserve University, School of Applied Social Sciences, supervision conference notes, 1939 (Box 53, Folder 55)
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS AND TAPES
  - Certificates and awards, oversize, 1966, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence records, Florence Hollis, 1942-1985 (Box 55)
  - [See Flat file] (Box 56)
  - Case records on index cards, A-Z, 1926-1971 (Box 57)
  - Psychological Perspective in Clinical Social Work, a Personal Perspective of How it Really Began," videocassette, Smith College, 1983 (Box 58)
  - Typology research, Watson, early content analysis and coded data, ca. 1953-1957 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Typology research, Kerr, early content analysis and coded data, 1956-1958 [?] (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Typology research, training kit, code sheets, 1964-1965 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Typology research, code sheets, record T1, interview 1 and interview 3, 1963 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Typology research, typology coding with Mitzi Montgomery, code sheets, 1971-1972 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Tapes of cases used in typology research
    - No. 1001 and 1002
      - Reel 1
        - No. 1001, side 1, Mr. Hays, interview 6, April 12, 1966 (Box 60)
        - No. 1002, side 2, Mr. and Mrs. Will, interview 5, April 12, 1966 (Box 60)
    - No. 1002
      - Reel 2
        - side 1, Mr. Will, interview 6, April 19, 1966 (Box 60)
        - side 2, Mrs. Will, interview 6, April 19, 1966 (Box 60)
      - Reel 3
        - side 1, Mr. Will, interview 7, April 26, 1966 (Box 60)
        - side 2, Mrs. Will, interview 8, May 3, 1966 (Box 60)
      - Reel 4
        - side 1, Mr. Will, interview 8, May 3, 1966 (Box 60)
        - side 2, Mrs. Will, interview 9, May 10, 1966 (Box 60)
      - Reel 5
        - side 1, Mr. Will, interview 9, May 10, 1966 (Box 60)
        - side 2, Mrs. Will, interview 10, May 17, 1966 (Box 60)
      - Reel 6
        - side 1, Mr. Will, interview 10, May 17, 1966 (Box 60)
    - No. 1003
      - Reel 1
        - side 1, Mr. Ewell, interview 6, October 13, 1966 (Box 60)
        - side 2, Mr. Ewell, interview 7, October 18, 1966 (Box 60)
      - Reel 2
        - side 1, Mr. Ewell, interview 8, October 25, 1966 (Box 60)
        - side 2, Mr. Ewell, interview 9, November 1, 1966 (Box 60)
      - Reel 3
        - side 1, Mr. Ewell, interview 10, November 8, 1966 (Box 60)
      - Reel 4
        - side 1, Mrs. Ewell, interview 8, October 10, 1966 (Box 60)
        - side 2, Mrs. Ewell, interview 9, October 20, 1966 (Box 60)
      - Reel 5
        - side 2, Mrs. Ewell, interview 10, October 27, 1966 (Box 60)
    - No. 1004
      - Reel 1
        - side 1, Mrs. Ritter, interview 10, October 9, 1966 (Box 60)
    - No. 1006
      - Reel 1
        - side 1, Mrs. Overton, interview 7, April 10, 1967 (Box 60)
      - Reel 2
        - side 1, Mrs. Overton, interview 8, April 14, 1967 (Box 60)
        - side 2, Mrs. Overton, interview 9, April 17, 1967 (Box 60)
      - Reel 3
        - side 1, Mrs. Overton, interview 10, April 21, 1967 (Box 60)
      - Reel 4
        - side 1, Mr. Overton, interview 5, April 13, 1967 (Box 60)
        - side 2, Mr. Overton, interview 6, April 18, 1967 (Box 60)
    - No. 1007
      - Reel 1
        - side 1, Mr. Murphy, interview 6, April 6, 1967 (Box 60)
      - Reel 2
        - side 1, Mr. Murphy, interview 7, April 13, 1967 (Box 60)
      - Reel 3
        - side 1, Mr. Murphy, interview 8, April 21, 1967 (Box 60)
      - Reel 4
        - side 1, Mrs. Murphy, interview 6, April 14, 1967 (Box 60)
      - Reel 5
        - side 1, Mrs. Murphy, interview 7, April 21, 1967 (Box 60)
      - Reel 6
        - side 1, joint interview: Mrs. Murphy, interview 8; Mr. Murphy, interview 9, April 27, 1967 (Box 60)
      - Reel 7
        - side 2, joint interview: Mrs. Murphy, interview 9; Mr. Murphy, interview 10, May 4, 1967 (Box 60)
      - Reel 8
        - side 1, joint interview: Mrs. Murphy interview 10; Mr. Murphy interview 11, May 17, 1967 (Box 60)
    - No. 1009
      - Reel 1
        - side 1, Mrs. James, interview 7, June 21, [196?] (Box 60)
      - Reel 2
        - side 1, Mrs. James, interview 8, June 28, [196?] (Box 60)
      - Reel 3
        - side 1, Mrs. James, interview 9, July 5, [196?] (Box 60)
      - Reel 4
        - side 1, Mrs. James, interview 10, July 12, [196?] (Box 60)
      - Reel 5
        - side 2, Mrs. James, interview [?], [July 196[?] (Box 60)
      - Reel 6
        - side 1, Mr. James, [interview 5?], June 22, 196? (Box 60)
      - Reel 7
        - side 1, Mr. James, [interview 6?], June 28, 196? (Box 60)
      - Reel 8
        - side 1, Mr. James, [interview 7 or interview 8], July 11, 196? or July 20, 196? (Box 60)
      - Reel 9
        - side 1, Mr. James, interview 9, July 25, [196?] (Box 60)
      - Reel 10
        - side 1, Mr. James, interview 10, August 2, [196?] (Box 60)
    - No. 1011
      - Reel 1
        - side 1, Mr. and Mrs. Kornblet, interview 6, May 2, 1967 (Box 60)
      - Reel 2
        - side 1, Mr. and Mrs. Kornblet, interview 7, May 29, 1967 (Box 60)
      - Reel 3
        - side 1, Mr. and Mrs. Kornblet, interview 8, July 11, 1967 (Box 60)
      - Reel 4
        - side 2, Mr. and Mrs. Kornblet, interview 9, July 25, 1967 (Box 60)
    - No. 1012
      - Reel 1
        - side 1, joint interview: Mr. Sully, interview 5; Mrs. Sully, interview 5, May 17, 1967 (Box 61)
      - Reel 2
        - side 1, joint interview: Mr. Sully, interview 6; Mrs. Sully, interview 6, May 23, 1967 (Box 61)
      - Reel 3
        - side 1, joint interview: Mr. Sully, interview 7; Mrs. Sully, interview 7, June 1, 1967 (Box 61)
      - Reel 4
        - side 1, joint interview [?]: Mr. Sully, interview 8 [?]; Mrs. Sully, interview 8 [?], [June 6, 1967 [?] (Box 61)
      - Reel 5
        - side 1, joint interview: Mr. Sully, interview 10; Mrs. Sully, interview 10 June 22, 1967 (Box 61)
    - No. 1021
      - Reel 1
        - side 1, Mr. Stridiron, interview 6, December 20, 1966 (Box 61)
        - side 2, Mr. Stridiron, interview 7, January 4, 1967 (Box 61)
      - Reel 2
        - side 1, Mr. Stridiron, interview 8, January 10, 1967 (Box 61)